bestsampleresume.com 2019-02-27

# Our Privacy Policy

We respect your right to privacy. We will never sell or rent your name, e-mail address and any other identifying information that you give us with any third party. 

For each visitor, our web server collects no information regarding the domain, location, route or e-mail address. We only check the IP address and use it for internal purpose. We use IP address for creating unique hits for our banners. 

By signing up for our FREE service, you agree to receive occasional e-mails from our company or our sponsors. You may remove yourself from these mailings at any time. 

**Third Party Advertising:**

We use Burst Media, Casale Media, BUDS INC, Google, RealCastMedia, Commission Junction, MaxWorldwide and other third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our Web site. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, please click here 

**Third Party Cookies:**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique 'cookie' on your browser. 

The third party ad network or server will be using technology for the links and advertisements, which appear on [www.bestsampleresume.com](http://www.bestsampleresume.com/) send directly to the browser. They will on their own get IP address when this happens. Some of the other technologies like JavaScript, Web Beacons and cookies will be used by the third-party advertiser for measuring the effectiveness of the ads or for personalizing the ad content you see. Our website does not have access or control over such cookies, which are used by our third-party advertiser. 

You can go through the respective privacy policies of such third-party advertisers for more information on the practices, along with instructions on how you can opt out from the same. Our website's policy does not apply to, and we will not be able to control any activities of, other websites or advertisers. 

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google's cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google's own privacy policies. 

**Links to other Websites:**

Our website may have links for other websites that may interest you. However, once you have to chosen to use those links for leaving our sites, you should know that we will have no control over the other website. Therefore, we will not be responsible for any privacy and protection of any kind of information, which you will be giving while you visit other sites and such sites are not governed by our privacy statements. Make sure that you exercise caution and look for the privacy statements that are applicable to the website that is in question. 

**About Google advertising:**

What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher.s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user.s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. [Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). 

If there are any issues with our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](http://www.bestsampleresume.com/contact-us.html).
